Contact

7815351758 (Mobile) wang.jason.010@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jason-wang-996a25a6 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

JavaScript Python Java

Languages

Chinese (Native or Bilingual) English (Full Professional)

Jason Wang

Software Development Engineer

Greater Seattle Area

Summary

GitHub: https://github.com/jawang94

I am a Nursing/International Business major turned Software Developer with a burning passion to positively impact the world.

Upon moving to Seattle I worked as Assistant Director of Eastside Tennis Center where I was critical in the daily operation and growth of the club.

After over one year I decided to leave my position and pursue my dream. Software Development. I began studying programming independently and attended a coding bootcamp in 2018 where I acquired high proficiency in Python, Javascript, and Java.

Experience

Self Employed Independent Software Developer November 2018 - Present

Eastside Tennis Center Assistant Director May 2016 - November 2017 (1 year 7 months) Kirkland, WA

Organized and directed all aspects of the Adult Program
Resolved all Private Lesson requests in a timely manner
Responsible for opening and closing the center as well as Front Desk
operations

Solo coached classes of up to 15 students, both Adult and Junior, up to a competitive level

Maintained a complete understanding of all operations, programs, staff, and scheduling

Assisted in directing and smoothly running Sanctioned USTA Tournaments

Education

Coding Dojo

Computer Software Engineering · (2018 - 2018)

Drexel University

International Business · (2014 - 2016)

Drexel University College of Nursing & Health Professions Division of Undergraduate Nursing

· (2012 - 2014)